

#### Contact

+233 50 385 3419

Tema, Ghana

#### **Tools Skills**

- Figma
- Adobe XD
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator

## Soft Skills

- HTML/CSS
- PHP (LARAVEL)

#### Education

• 2019 - 2020

Diploma Graphics & Web Design IPMC

2023 - Present
BTECH. COMP. SCIENCE
Koforidua Technical University
(KTU)

## **Portfolio**

Kenneth Ashartey

## Languages

English

Ga-Dangme

Twi

# Kenneth Ashartey

**UX UI Designer** 

## **About Me**

I am a mid-level UI/UX designer with one and a half years of professional experience in the field. My expertise lies in conceptualizing and designing engaging software products that are both aesthetically appealing and highly functional. With strong problem-solving abilities and creative skills, I am able to deliver effective solutions that satisfy the needs of both the customer and the end-user.

## Experience

2021-2022

#### **Graphics Designer**

**Printwell Communications** 

- Developed and maintained brand identities, ensuring cohesive and visually appealing branding across all platforms.
- Designed eye-catching advertisement banners for various marketing campaigns.
- Managed the end-to-end process of printing assignments.
- 2022-2023

## **UX UI Designer**

Graphics Intel - oyeh/ Nufiala

- Design of mobile applications from concept to launch
- Created wireframes, user flows, and visual designs for new features and enhancements
- Prototyping
- 2023-2024

#### **UX UI Designer**

Property Management Console(PMC)

- Responsible for the design of web and mobile applications
- Conducted user research
- Created wireframes and visual designs for new features and enhancements
- Responsible for development of high-fidelity prototypes
- 2024 Present

## **UX UI Designer**

Uniox - in development